(Amy:)Well, you know,
as long as you're happy.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
I am. (chuckles)
(Amy:)And Rick said you could bring in
your old one to recycle it.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Uh, no, no, no, thank you.
(Amy:)Oh, but he said
you can get store credit.
(Sheldon:)Well, no, I just...
I-I don't want to recycle it.
(Sheldon:)And I don't want store credit.
(Amy:)But why wouldn't...
(Sheldon:)Can we please change
the subject?
O-Okay.
(Amy:)How 'bout we change it to why
you're being weird about this?
(Sheldon:)I'm not being weird.
(Amy(on Skype):)I...
(Sheldon:)It's hard to explain.
(Amy:)Sheldon, just tell me.
(Sheldon:)It might be easier to show you.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)We'd have to take your car.
(Penny:)All right.
(Sheldon:)And I'm gonna need you to sign
a nondisclosure agreement.
(Amy:)Well, I signed one
before we slept together.
(Amy:)Why not now?